<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">siti luthfa humairah</string>
    <string name="anabelle_nama">Anabelle</string>
    <string name="string_nama">Name</string>
    <string name="string_alamat">Address</string>
    <string name="string_hobi">Hobby</string>
    <string name="string_jurusan">Major</string>
    <string name="string_kembali">Back</string>
    <string name="string_filmgenre">movie genre</string>
    <string name="string_tekan_poster_film_untuk_membuka_galeri">" (Tap the movie poster to open the gallery)"</string>
    <string name="string_nonton_film">Watching movies</string>
    <string name="anabelle_deskripsi">Annabele is based on a true story. In 1967, a husband and wife living in Santa Monica were informed, John Form (Ward Horton) and Mia Form (Annabelle Wallis). It was discovered that the family were followers of the Ram (Satanic) cult.</string>
    <string name="theconjuring_nama">" The Conjuring "</string>
    <string name="anabelle_genre">Horror</string>
    <string name="the_conjuring_genre">Horror</string>
    <string name="the_conjuring_deskripsi">CONJURING 3 DEVIL MADE ME DO IT is based on a court case known by the same name. The story is on November 24, 1981 in Brookfield, Connecticut, Arne Cheyenne Johnson is tried in first degree murder for the death of a landlord named Alan Bono. The case became famous because it involved, for the first time, elements of \"demon possession\" in a murder trial.</string>
    <string name="the_nun">The Nun</string>
    <string name="the_nun_deskripsi">The story in the film The Nun begins when the Vatican authorities receive reports of the death of a nun in Romania. This nun was reported to have died under mysterious circumstances. The Vatican then sent an envoy named Father Burke (Demián Bichir) to Romania to investigate this case.</string>
    <string name="the_nun_genre">Horror</string>
    <string name="love_rosie">Love Rosie</string>
    <string name="love_rosie_genre">Romance</string>
    <string name="love_rosie_deskripsi">Love Rosie is a romantic comedy drama film that tells the story of Rosie Dune and Alex Stewart who have been in a friendly relationship since they were 5 years old.</string>
    <string name="before_sunrise">Before Sunrise</string>
    <string name="before_sunrise_genre">Romance</string>
    <string name="before_surise_deskripsi">Before Sunrise is a 1995 romantic drama film. The film tells the story of Jesse, a young American man, and Céline, a young French woman, who coincidentally meet and exchange ideas on the Eurail train.</string>
    <string name="a_walk_to_remember">A Walk to Remember</string>
    <string name="a_walk_to_remember_genre">Romance</string>
    <string name="a_walk_to_remember_deskripsi">This film is an American romantic drama that tells the love story of a nerdy girl and a boy who is popular at school</string>
    <string name="cek_toko_sebelah">Cek Toko Sebelah</string>
    <string name="cek_toko_sebelah_genre">Comedy</string>
    <string name="cek_toko_sebelah_deskripsi">Cek Toko Next is an Indonesian comedy film. The story of this film is based on the reality of the Chinese ethnicity when the children grow up, go to high school, and sadly end up working in their own parents\' shop.</string>
    <string name="susah_sinyal">Susah Sinyal</string>
    <string name="susah_sinyal_genre">Comedy</string>
    <string name="susah_sinyal_deskripsi">This film focuses on the life of a mother named Ellen (Adinia Wirasti) who works as a famous lawyer. Unfortunately, because of this time-consuming job, Ellen often doesn\'t have time for her only daughter, Kiara (Aurora Ribero).</string>
    <string name="marmut_merah_jambu">Marmut Merah Jambu</string>
    <string name="marmut_merah_jambu_genre">Comedy</string>
    <string name="marmut_merah_jambu_deskripsi">Pink Guinea Pig\", \"Comedy\",             Dika tells the story of his first love in high school with a girl named Ina Mangunkusumo. The story of when he and his friend Bertus formed a detective group, and also his friendship with Cindy.</string>
    <string name="horror">Horror</string>
    <string name="romance">Romance</string>
    <string name="comedy">Comedy</string>
    <string name="nama">Name</string>
    <string name="alamat">Base</string>
    <string name="nim">NIM</string>
    <string name="hobi">Hobby</string>
    <string name="jurusan">Major</string>
    <string name="biodata_mahasiswa">Profile</string>
</resources>